[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Abraham Lincoln had no middle name",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Germany drinksthemost beerin theworld per person.",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question":"Ronald Reagan was a waiter during high school.",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question":"The kids’ bathroom on The Brady Bunch didn’t have a toilet.",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Nemo is a puffer fish.",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "John Lennon’s middle name was Edward",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Broccoli was once banned from the White House",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Japan hassquarewatermelons.",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Pinocchio was the first animated, full-color Walt Disney feature film.",
        "answer": false,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "There was noWorld Seriesin 1994",
        "answer": true,
        "options": [
            {
                "option": true
            },
            {
                "option": false
            },
            {
                "option": "Skip"
            }
        ]
    }
]